Excuse me for the camera.
Which one is the comment?
This one.
I did it!
Hello.
Good evening.
Good evening, good evening.
I came to play.
Thank you.
Can I look for a model angle?
What should I do?
It's dry.
Hello.
My hair is cute.
My makeup is cute.
My hair and makeup are different from
usual.
I had a shooting today.
So, my makeup is different from usual.
My makeup is different from usual.
I don't care about it.
It looks like autumn.
My hair is a little thin.
I don't want to touch it.
I took out my sweater.
Long sleeves. I've noticed that it's
surprisingly cold here for a few days,
and I don't wear half-sleeves very much.
It's basically long sleeves.
Good evening.
Will it get hot again?
This summer was a little cool, wasn't it?
It was easy to spend.
Anyway, the weather is really bad, but it
's raining again today.
I don't like rain, but I'm not wearing it
now, but I was wearing long shoes at the
previous site.
I can't wear long shoes unless it's a
rainy day, so I was happy with that.
Good evening, good evening, yes, my skin
is so strong, isn't it?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I wonder how much of this is conveyed to
the audience.
I'm worried because it's different from
usual.
What? I got something like an aurora.
Wow!
Good evening.
Good evening, good evening.
I feel like I should proceed without
saying good evening.
I'm going to do the homework from the
previous members.
next member
Thank you
Ta-da!
To the next member, let me hear the
backstory of the audition
Mao
Oh, it's nostalgic! Look at this
I'm going to do it with this name
Do you still do it now?
I don't know what it meant at the time
I don't know if it's true, but it's not
good to have a letter in class, but when
I was in class, I had a letter or
something.
When I was turning my legs, I was doing
it with Nagi Yoripipipi.
I was doing something like dividing the
scene with Chan.
I was doing it properly
Oh, I have a homework
The back story of the audition
Back story? The back story of the
audition?
What is it?
When I auditioned
I was drawing every time
I used to draw a picture before the
audition, but it wasn't a picture I drew
before the audition, but I drew a picture
every time for the audition.
We, the 5th generation of Nagizaka46, had
a 5-hour screening and the next one was
the final screening.
I did 3 or 4 self-pros, so I drew 3 or 4
of them.
I drew wood and watercolors.
I'm not sure if I'm being silly or not.
I didn't think about whether I would win
or lose the audition.
I didn't think much about it.
I don't know what it means.
I'm really sorry.
I thought I did what I could do now with
all my strength.
That's how I felt when I auditioned.
So I always draw with all my strength.
My self-promotion was a mess in the final
evaluation.
It was a mess, but I wrote it all down
and practiced it as it is.
What song did I sing? I don't remember
what I sang, but I sang a few songs.
I sang something a long time ago, but I
sang something a long time ago, but I
sang something a long time ago
Oh, but the song I sang is a bit of a ho
ax, but according to rumors, I have heard
that there are many people who sing Aimy
on's Marigold in auditions.
I didn't know that there are many people
who sing.
Is it easy to sing? It's a good song, isn
't it? Oh, it shines on a regular basis.
amazing
It's amazing.
Aya always sings for me when I go to
karaoke.
So I have Aya's handwriting.
I think it's like this.
I was with Tomisato all the time.
Since I started to audition locally, I've
been with Tomisato all the time.
The group was the same, so it was all the
same.
And then there was the one in the next
group.
I was nervous.
Also, at the audition venue,
Mayu-sen bento was placed.
I was really surprised that there was a
Mayu-sen bento.
I was really happy about that.
I remember eating it with care.
I remember it well, isn't it good like
this?
Do you have anything else you want to
ask?
It's good, isn't it?
Well, let's hold the Nogiyobi
Championship.
Yes, so this week's competition is to
bring out the king.
There are a lot of shogi pieces in the
box, so let's draw the king or the king.
Let's play the 6th note.
Is it the 5th note?
Which one is the intonation?
The person who plays the 5th note the
fastest in the week will receive a
wonderful present.
However, if you choose carefully, you
will know, so put your hand in and take a
piece within 3 seconds.
This is it.
There is a box that is too big to put the
shogi piece in, so it seems that the king
will be drawn from the corner.
So let's go
Can I start this too?
How do you read this?
Hisha, I know this.
Gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold,
gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold,
gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold, gold
Gyokusho Gyokusho I should have done it
with my grandfather
I forgot it already. It's a little
difficult to write, but it came out with
the 8th one
Yes, it looks like this
Shogi, isn't it?
It's too bad to fly diagonally
Hisha?
Kaku?
Hisha and Kaku
I heard
Kaku
Samurai?
Gyo?
Kaku
Kaku Gyo?
Kaku is diagonal
Hisha?
I don't know
Difficult
It's hard, isn't it?
Well, I want to be the best in Igo Shogi,
but I don't have the motivation to do it.
I was reading Hikaru no Go just now, but
I didn't know the rules.
I can't play chess either.
I don't know. I don't know chess better.
I just wanted to come out and play on the
stone of the sage of Harry Potter.
I just wanted to come out and do it with
the will of a Harry Potter sage.
Also, in the Christmas season of Harry
Potter,
Is that the will of a sage?
I saw Ron and Harry doing it together in
front of the tree.
I thought I wanted to do it.
Well, that's the end of it.
My forehead is shiny. Stop it!
No, it's not like that.
It's not like that.
I just got my make-up done today, so it's
just like that.
So, from now on, free talk.
Should I decide the homework before the
free talk?
No, that's a little...
Can I announce the next member?
Is it too soon?
Is it a little too soon?
It's too soon.
Well, I'm going to talk about it in the
second half.
I'm going to talk about it in the second
half of the video, but I'm going to talk
about the return of Jingu, the return of
the tour, and I'm going to talk about it
in the second half of the video, but I'm
going to talk about it in the second half
of the video, but I'm going to talk about
it in the second half of the video, but I
'm going to talk about it in the second
half of the video, but I'm going to talk
about it in the second half of the video,
but I'm going to talk about it in the
second half of the video, but I'm going
to talk about it in the second half of
the video, but I'm going to talk about it
in the second half of the video, but I'm
going to talk about it in the second half
of the video, but I'm going to talk about
it in the second half of the video, but I
'm going to talk about it in the second
half of the video, but I'm going to talk
about it in the second half of
Actually, I was a detective.
Did you know?
Detective Inoue
I want you to tell me that.
It was added from Yokohama Park.
A detective corner was added from Yokoh
ama Park.
I was given an invitation.
What do you think the manager said?
What do you think I was told?
Detective
Please do Furuhata Ninzaburo
I was told
Furuhata Ninzaburo?
I don't know if it's not my generation
I searched for Furuhata Ninzaburo's video
I thought it was like this
I tried it
I tried it, but as a manager
But for me, it's not like that at all.
Then I was told that I want to do the Fur
uhata-Ninzaburo of Zakoshi-san.
I was like, that's impossible!
That's not the Furuhata-Ninzaburo!
It's like...
Think about it, everyone.
If you have seen the scene of the
national tour of the famous detective In
oue,
I want you to imagine it, but if that
music was playing and I said pachinko,
I was like, what should I do?
So I couldn't do it.
I was in a hurry.
I thought it might be impossible, so I
said I'll do my best.
I didn't do it.
It was fun.
It was really fun.
It's true that I'm a criminal, but I was
a detective every day.
What if I get a summary of that part?
It might be okay.
I'm scared if I get a summary.
I'm scared.
I haven't seen it yet.
That's right.
That's right, so I know you want to see
it, but it's a little embarrassing.
Is it a bonus or something?
Maybe one day.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
What should I do?
My hairstyle is so different from usual.
Are you okay?
Just in case, I brought a comb to cover
my hair.
So I brought it with me.
Should I put it on?
I think it looks better if I put it on.
What should I do?
Is it okay?
There are people who say that I have a
lot of bald hair on a regular basis.
It seems to be worrisome.
Are you uncomfortable?
No, it's not like that.
It's not like that.
I believe it's not like that.
Is it better not to put it on?
Is it different?
Which do you prefer, down or up?
I'll go with this for now.
That's the end of the Meitante corner.
What else?
I have summer break.
I want to talk about Mt. Fuji.
But it's all night long.
I want to hear about Vira.
Vira, right?
It was fun. I could only go for a day,
but there was an emotional scene, and
everyone went into the pool, and everyone
went into a small hot spring.
It was really fun. It's really youthful.
On the other hand, I was too excited to
take a picture, so I couldn't take it at
all.
So, surprisingly, the memories are only
in my heart.
It's like that, but I had a lot of fun.
Is this going? I don't know.
I don't know, but the other member and I
are going home in the middle of the trip.
I don't know if the other member is
going, so for the time being...
Oh, he's going? Is it Saktan?
He's going. I wonder if he's going.
Saktan and I were supposed to go home
together,
So it was fun to go home while talking in
the car.
There was also such a thing at Kanagawa
Kombi.
Everyone was carrying one by one.
I had a lot of Japanese products, so I
brought seafood.
I bought a lot of seafood.
I really wanted to do that.
I wanted to do abalone fried rice.
But abalone is so expensive.
It was so expensive that I was surprised.
Before I said I would buy it, I couldn't
go back.
But it was delicious.
I bought something like ayu and squid
that would be fun if there was something
like that.
Cheat day. That's right. It was a cheat
day.
It was a reward for us.
Chihikawa is similar.
Is Chihikawa similar?
I don't know Chihikawa.
I can't get into it at all.
Chihikawa...
I always thought that 80% was Chihikawa.
I thought it was Chii-kawa, but it was H
achibaru.
Chii-kawa has nothing.
It looks like Hachibaru.
It has a pattern and has a long ear like
a rabbit.
What is this?
Is it Momonga?
It looks like Momonga.
I thought the protagonist was the most
simple and the best.
I didn't know that.
I don't know much about it, but many of
my friends watch Chikawa movies and are
into her.
Many of my friends say they like Seiren-
chan.
Seiren-chan. The one in red, black and
white.
Is it okay to say Seiren-chan? I don't
know.
So, shall we decide on our homework?
Do you want to decide the topic one by
one?
The topic?
Yes.
I'll do it after I announce the next
member.
The next member is...
Well...
It's Aruno Nakanishi!
Yay!
I'm glad I got it right.
It doesn't matter if it's a senior or a
junior.
It's kind of easy.
Aruno Nakanishi.
What is it?
I don't know.
What is it? What is it?
What is it?
Oh, do you want me to do an impersonation
of Zakoshi-san?
Who is it?
I think it's better not to do it.
I'll do an impersonation of Zakoshi-san's
GURUHATANI ZAMURO.
Show me your model.
That's right.
No, let's do that.
Because that person is me.
Did you see that?
During the construction.
I was picked as a mean mom during the
procession.
I'm going to do it again.
I'm going to look up if the kanji is
scary.
I know that kanji is weak.
I also know that the characters are
dirty.
I'm going to be punished.
My stomach hurts.
I'm not like that.
I'm doing it in a bad way, so it doesn't
hurt my stomach.
I'm looking forward to it.
Is there anything you want me to do?
I have three minutes left.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at all-nighters.
I don't have a neck.
I don't have a neck, I don't have a neck,
I don't have a neck, I don't have a neck
It's the first time I've heard the name
of Sampaku-gan.
I think it's different.
I haven't seen Alpurgis yet.
Madomagine.
No spoilers, right?
I can't say it even if I saw it.
I want to see it.
This face.
I saw it in the bookstore. Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Blind Eye?
I don't think there's a contact.
I'm watching Sensara.
I'm watching Toyotomi Brothers.
Thank you.
Thank you Thank you Thank you Thank you
Thank you Thank you Thank you Thank
I hope you have a good time with me.
Tomorrow, the day after tomorrow, or the
day after tomorrow.
Well, it's about time to say goodbye.
I don't know how to say goodbye every
time.
Oh, I did it.
So, goodbye.
Let's meet again somewhere.
See you.
Is the live broadcast over?
Yes, it's over.